Tsuruno is the strongest.
She's stronger than everyone.
And since she's so strong, she's okay.
Tsuruno, stop.
I am the strongest.
What happened, Yachiyo? Are you okay?
She rejected my connect.
You're kidding. But how come?
What the heck happened?
Was our timing off or something?
I don't know.
But I think it's good we stopped our attack when we did.
Now what are we supposed to do?
Don't worry. I will save everyone.
I think we should get going.
Uh-oh.
What did we do?
Tsuruno is one of the Magius's best creations.
How dare they treat her so rough?
Those darn poop heads.
Now I'm really, really, really mad.
Toka.
Why do things turn out like this?
She's strong.
The strongest magical girl ever.
That's why she's not hurt.
She's A-OK.
Yachiyo, try connecting again.
Sorry.
I can't.
Huh?
I guess I didn't know her after all.
But you know her the best!
I don't.
I never really knew her.
I don't think she'll cause the second one to 21 Ran.
Who's there?
Okay.
I mean, it's not far too much.
He's funny.
I know she says.
At the start, I had a feeling our plan wasn't going to work.
Where is this?
I told myself I knew Tsuruno, and I thought I did, but I didn't.
Yachiyo? What's wrong? Yachiyo!
Deep down, I knew the truth. I didn't know or understand Tsuruno at all.
I refused to admit it to myself. I completely shut it out.
I guess the reason was I didn't want to be right, and so I chose the kind of person I wanted her to be.
I... I didn't bother learning who she was.
I'm Tsuruno Yui, the magical girl. The strongest.
Tsuruno?
I always act cheerful and energetic, because that's who I have to be.
That's right, I have to be that girl.
I've had to be that girl.
That day.
According to my fortune, today is going to be the luckiest day of my life. Really?
Hold on. You promised you wouldn't tell any more fortunes, Mel.
Your predictions always end up being accurate. So if the result is unfavorable...
Hey, this is that past event I saw in the Memory Museum.
If she gets a bad result, then we'll just work hard to stop it.
Here you go, folks!
One large Mopo sweet and sour pork! It's Bon Bon's eye specialty!
Hey there, Master!
Hi, Tsuruno. You free?
Yeah, only for a couple seconds.
We're packed today, like super busy!
Uh, well, we just spotted a witch that came here from Daito Ward.
But I'm here with everyone already.
So if you can't come, it's okay. We'll handle it.
I'm sorry. It's rare for us to get a reservation for such a large group.
No. Stay and help your parents.
Thanks a lot, Master Yachiyo.
I believed her, so I stayed at work and didn't help with that witch.
Mel died? For real?
But, like, you said you guys could handle it.
I know, but the witch was too strong.
It's my fault. I should've gone.
What? No. It was bad luck.
If I'd have been there with them, Mel wouldn't have died.
There's nothing we could do.
If you were there, it wouldn't have changed anything.
They don't think I'm strong enough to matter.
Don't blame yourself for it, Tsuruno.
It's no one's fault.
It's my fault for being weak.
Mel was killed because I'm weak.
No, Tsuruno! That's not true!
I have to get stronger.
I failed.
So now, I must get stronger.
Mel was killed because I was weak.
That's not true!
I just heard Mifuyu's missing!
It's true.
She's not answering my calls.
I still had so much I wanted to learn from Mifuyu, too.
Why do I have to protect Senkyo Ward on my own?
Because Momoko's training new magical girls.
If there's anything you need to know about magical girls, just hit me up.
Thanks, Momoko. You're the best!
Even Momoko doesn't want to be around me.
If you think it's too much for you...
Not even Master Gachiyo!
I'm the strongest magical girl, so I can handle anything!
I have to.
I don't have a choice.
I have to be the strongest magical girl.
Otherwise...
Everyone's going to turn their backs on me.
I have to work harder.
I can't complain about the strain.
If they see I'm worried about something, they'll stop trusting me.
I'm Tsuda-no the magical girl.
I'm always cheerful and energetic and strong.
Are you okay?
That was nothing! I could do this all day!
I can't count on Yachiyo anymore.
Even if she says I can sit this fight out, I can't trust her.
I've got loads of energy to spare!
That's why I'll always win!
I'm the strongest.
And now, I'm wondering how long I have to keep acting this way.
A customer!
Welcome to Chinese Restaurant Bon Banzai!
I need to be an example to all the other magical girls in Kamehama.
More cheerful, more energetic.
I need to be the strongest of them all.
None of that stuff matters.
Be yourself and that's enough!
I have to work harder.
I have to work harder!
You and your fortunes!
What part of this is lucky?
This is awful!
It's not!
I am lucky!
I have to work harder.
Wait, is this...?
Oh no...
This is when I...
I...
No!
Saruna, it's not what you think!
It's not!
I can't put up this front anymore.
I don't want to.
I'm done.
I don't have anything left to offer.
I...
You're wrong, you too!
Now I know what went wrong.
It's my fault.
I put too much pressure on her.
Yachiyo!
That was weird...
Wasn't it?
The Kinect linked us with her subconscious...
Fino's the strongest magical girl!
They stronger than anyone!
Anyone!
You can stop now!
We know the truth!
Wake up!
She's strong and she's okay!
She's just fine!
You're not okay at all!
Felicia...
You're not as strong as you say!
So quit lying already!
Quit hiding how you really feel!
Be honest!
You're gonna kill yourself if you're not!
Felicia...
Stay back!
Oh, shut up!
You're the same as her!
I admit it.
It's my fault she's suffering.
I pushed her to get stronger and stronger.
I put the pressure on her that led to this.
Or...
It'll get closer to it...
Maybe you were, but you weren't even tougher on yourself.
But nobody's so strong they can go it alone.
Ask yourself this, how do you want Sudono to be from now on?
All I want is for her to stop pretending.
Alone, we're not strong enough, but together we are.
Iroha.
Could someone please help?
Looks like I made it right on time.
Momoku!
Ugh, don't be ridiculous.
You barely made it in time.
Nifuyu!
We can keep the witches off your back.
Now go and save Sudono.
Sudono!
Hurry, take the shot!
Let's connect and bring her back.
Right.
I know you never wanted to be the strongest of us, but you never had to be.
There were enough of us to share the burden.
Remember, we're always here for you and ready to listen.
I'm sorry, Sudono.
Let's começa.
Huh.
Come on, it's our turn.
Out of us all, Mommy is the strongest and always took the time to teach us.
But she pushed herself too hard.
I failed, I failed everyone.
Now it's up to me to save them.
She's busted out! Hurry!
We want our Mommy back!
Time to come back to us, Mommy!
Kiro, do it!
We did it!
We're up!
Right!
Head out!
The Witches are leaving.
It worked!
We make a good team, huh?
You can be such a pain.
Thanks, everyone. I'm sorry.
We're glad you're back.
Yachiyo?
Just relax.
Are you okay, Tsuruno?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, guys.
You don't need to apologize.
I'm sorry, Tsuruno.
Felicia, I'm sorry for everything.
O-okay.
Don't feel bad.
Seriously, everyone makes mistakes.
Fixing them's all that matters.
Yes, you're right.
Momoko, Mifuyu, thank you for helping bring Tsuruno back to us.
It doesn't even begin to make up for what I've done.
The important thing is, we're together again, and that's all that matters.
Together again? This is great!
The violent winds that slammed into Kamehama have finally subsided.
The supercell is still active, though.
It has changed course and is now heading straight for Mitakihara.
Oh no.
Valpurgis Noct is heading for our town.
We have to get back home.
But she can't be there when Valpurgis Noct arrives.
Come on, let's go.
What?
Iroha.
I hope you find your friends and get through to them.
I better hurry.
What the heck?
Are you feeling better?
Oh yeah.
Way better than before, for sure.
Iroha.
Do you really think they are going to accept you?
You're way different from them, you know.
Remember, when I was weak, you offered to give me a hand?
I don't.
But I...
I want...
To go with them, you can't.
You're different.
They're nothing like you.
I don't need to be strong to beat these things.
That's it.
Telka!
Iroha Tamaki!
Talk to me.
Tell me why you're doing this.
I don't have to tell you a darn thing, darn it.
I had an amazing plan and you ruined it!
But your plan was horrible.
Kidnapping people?
Destroying the town?
Honestly!
Like I keep telling everyone,
it was the only way to save us magical girls!
I know you.
You're not the kind of girl who would do this.
What do you mean you know me?
Who do you think you are?
Toka, enough is enough.
Nemuro!
Hey, big sis.
I've missed you.
Big sis?
You mean you know this person, Nemuro?
No, we do.
I'm sorry, but I've been lying to you.
But now, there's no reason to hide the truth from everyone anymore.
What are you doing?
It's time I told both of you the truth.
The truth about us.
And everything that's happened.